You guys must be grinning on the inside when you get asked these questions!
The feel-good question grand prix!
Okay, so the third one is Suzuki.
I don't think I've put it out there. Even if there was a question that made me grin, I don't think I would have answered it.
Pocker face.
Gutsy, really.
The question that makes you grin.
Oh, that one?
I don't like it.
I don't like that question.
Questions you don't want to be attracted to.
How much do you pay?
Hey, I'll take one.
I'll answer.
I've got a pee in my pocket from Saga.
Arle-wide Triple Roll Yo Night
My pretty for you I'm sorry for being a pain in the ass
Wish to come true with you
Hit me now, hit me now
If it's words, I don't need them anymore
It's up now, it's up now
You and me, so we make
How can you please me?
What's that you're asking from above now
Can you please me? It's up now, it's up now, you and me, so we make
That's so bad.
You definitely want to please me.
I've never been asked that before.
I've never been asked.
They don't think that.
They don't think so.
You've never asked me, have you?
I've never been asked.
I don't have that image.
Okay, then.
I think that's enough, don't you?
You're very popular.
I get that a lot.
No, thank you.
What do you see?
I don't think you're popular with the opposite sex.
Of course you think I'm popular.
I was wrong.
I'm weak.
I have to fight.
Why don't you just go home?
What's the hardest question you've ever had to answer?
I feel like I'm answering all of them.
I do.
If you have a question you don't feel comfortable answering...
I'll just...
I think he's just grazing it.
I think I change it.
No, I don't.
At first, I'd talk about it as I went along.
I'll go where I'm comfortable.
It's better to meet them where you feel comfortable.
Shin-chan is the one who's given me the most trouble.
The one who's given me the most trouble so far...
It's Shin-chan
When I'm trying to hold back my tears
He keeps waiting for me to cry
Uh...
It's not like I'm doing an interview or anything.
but when I cry...
How do you feel?
The last thing I want is to be asked about my medical treatment when I'm crying.
I didn't want to tell you.
It's nice to meet you. You don't come to see me that often?
Oh, okay. Well, when you said it...
I was in trouble.
When you're crying and you can't say anything.
I have to talk.
You say, but you must have thought of a question good enough to make me really messed up.
Mochi! Mochi! Mochi!
No, I think only Hana can guess this one now.
I can't guess.
I don't think only Hana would think so.
So, for now, the flowers are the last.
Yes, that's right.
It's totally different.
The way you're saying it.
I won't be able to see you anyway.
Here they are.
You seem to be the most modern among the members, but what is popular now?
I see.
Yuzu is always talking about new things, new releases, and things that we think are good to use, which are also popular,
I think that's why they enjoy talking about it like this.
That's for sure.
I really like talking about these things to the members.
But I might get in trouble if I am asked about it in an interview.
It's going to change.
I'm going to change.
Because, you know.
You're imitating others, so you're the second centimeter.
So that's how it is.
I'm not on the cutting edge.
Then ask the role model I'm aiming for.
Oh, no.
None.
None?
Write back.
What!
They're going to say "None"?
They're going to say none.
Backtrack?
A rewrite.
What should I do?
Okay, what's next, Mr. Suzuki?
Okay, now, go back and rewrite it.
Let me put my answer.
Okay.
Then, what kind of snacks do you recommend?
Ah.
Uh...
Good.
Yes.
This is good.
Yes, every time I see Yuzu, everyone brings in their own gifts, but Yuzu has the image of being particular about it.
Yuzu is always particular about it,
I always get the image that they are particular about it, so they are always smiling and telling me how delicious it is.
I thought they would tell me how delicious it is.
I'm sure of it.
I thought that's true.
Because of the flowers.
And I've changed, too.
Oh, really?
I'm probably the most particular about the gifts.
This is the best one.
It's good.
I did it.
I rewrote it, Aya.
I rewrote it.
Okay, Aya, please.
I'll take 10th place.
Okay.
What's so attractive about Mara Tang?
Oh, it looks good, it looks good, it looks good.
I'm getting a little tired of this one.
What?
Bored.
Why? Why are you saying you like it so much lately?
It's not that I like it lately, it's just that I want to have some ma lattang for dinner today,
That's all.
But you go there often with your friends, right?
Yes, I do.
My friends are into it too.
Yes, my friends are into it too.
I thought I told you before that the Mara Tan craze has been coming recently,
So you like it this way.
Yeah.
I think that's enough, please go home.
Oh.
You'll have to rewrite it.
That's enough.
Hang in there, guys.
I don't have any more prospects, but I'll rewrite it just in case.
There are no more.
I'm adding more and more, but haven't I written about 10 things?
He wrote them as illustrations.
It really shows your personality, doesn't it, Yuzuki?
Isn't Yuzuki's scale long?
Yes, it is.
Yuzu is already a pain in the ass.
I don't want to rewrite anymore.
I don't want to say "rewrite" either.
I'll go ahead.
Okay.
Okay, then.
Jang-jang.
I think you have great taste, but why don't you make something produced by Yuzu?
That would be nice.
What is it? This.
It's true that when Yuzuki told us about his true method in the interview, he said, "I don't really want to do anything on my own,
I thought, "There is not much I want to do by myself.
But on the contrary, he always says in his articles that he wants to produce.
You've said that.
Oh, that's right.
You've said that yourself.
He doesn't ask me what I want to do.
That's true, that's true.
You're asking yourself what you want to do.
If someone asks me if I don't want to produce, I would be very angry.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yay.
Good questions.
Those are two great ones.
Yes.
Last one.
KAN-chan, right?
I'm sure, because we've been partners for 10 years.
We've been partners for 10 years, right?
I couldn't answer correctly.
Yes, I can.
Do you have a positive image?
Do you have a negative one?
Ah, it's over.
Now.
You didn't guess.
It's now.
Kojima, blow again.
I already blew it back up.
Go for it.
So you two don't have that perspective.
But Hana is going to be asked if she's Hana
But Hana's more likely to be asked, so Yuzuki's not likely to be asked
Side is more my type
Okay, okay, on the side.
I'm standing.
I'm on the side.
I'll have to bend that part.
You're right, they do go together.
Okay, so, did you two get it?
Yes, sir.
So they're the same?
Not exactly.
They're a little bit the same.
Then open them all at once.
Okay.
Are you good at making sweets? Is there anything you want to make right now?
What are you best at making?
Look at it now.
Here is the correct answer.
You don't look like you can cook, but you are actually low at making sweets.
Same here.
Correct answer.
Finally, here it is.
Maybe some of you know that I'm good at it.
That's right.
I had an image of the members when I said that, didn't I?
Maybe I had an image of the members.
I don't know if you have recently become a fan or not.
That's true.
We don't show much these days.
That's right. I've been making music for a long time, doing things like the Corona Disaster.
If you listen to this, you'll think, "Oh, that's nice.
I see. That's true.
But it was all good.
Really?
You did it after you rewrote it.
I think I rewrote it twice.
You submitted three.
You submitted three?
Thank you, Mari Fujikawa.
If you want to be asked this question, it means you are appealing that you have girl power, right?
That's right.
It's true.
I have girl power.
Photography, sweets, producing, etc.
You want to show that you have girl power.
I'm a mom, and I'm a kisser.
Marriage, I want to be number one in the ranking of people I want to marry," she says.
It's really not true.
I think it's crazy.
To Mr. Fasting, ranking the Ameflayan members you want to marry,
To be number one,
Layers, please vote for Yuzuki.
Honestly.
You really shouldn't do it.
But you really shouldn't vote for Hana, either.
I think it's best if I don't do it to you.
Well, then, since you moaned.
I wanted to do it four times.
Four times?
Oh, yeah.
Three times.
You send him home every day with a grin on your face,
I'm happy for you,
But you've had so many.
It's a little too much.
On the contrary, it's too much,
There are several effects.
Yes.
Which one?
Bye-bye.